
export const Questions = [
    {
      "category": "Animals",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "A slug's blood is green.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "The movie The Nightmare before Christmas was all done with physical objects.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Greenland is almost as big as Africa.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "The music video to The Buggle Video Killed the Radio Starwas the first music video to broadcast on MTV.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Gumbo is a stew that originated in Louisiana.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "'Undertale' is an RPG created by Toby Fox and released in 2015.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Half-Life 2 runs on the Source Engine.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In Kill La Kill, the weapon of the main protagonist is a katana. ",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In 'Sonic Adventure', you are able to transform into Super Sonic at will after completing the main story.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science & Nature",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "An atom contains a nucleus.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    }
  ]
